Vinh Huynh

ABOUT ME

I am an entry level developer. I am well-versed in the languages of the web and enjoy finding creative solutions to an array of challenges. My design sensibilities allow me to unite function & form effectively and create outstanding user experiences.

LINKEDIN

www.linkedin.com/in/vinh-huynh

PORTFOLIO

www.vinh512.github.io

GITHUB

www.github.com/Vinh512

SKILLS

Javascript	jQuery	Java	SQL	Photoshop
HTML	Bootstrap	JSP	Git / GitHub	Illustrator
CSS	React	Servlets	NetBeans	3DS Max

PROJECTS

Paper, **Pencil**, **Scissors** - A platform for teachers to request classroom supplies from generous donors. Worked on a team of developers and UX designers to implement their design and functionality.

Peer Pulse - An app that facilitates decision-making allowing users to submit and vote for activities in which the most-voted result is chosen. Worked on a team of developers using React and Firebase.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance - Front	End Developer	/ Digital Artist	2016 - Present
-------------------	---------------	------------------	----------------

• 3D Artist working on VR games for indie Austin studio

KingsIsle Entertainment - Digital Artist 2011 - 2016

- Worked on the highly successful Wizards 101 and Pirate 101
- Designed and created various art assets & environments

Sony Computer Entertainment America - Scan Artist Contractor 2010 - 2011

- Optimized and aligned 3D head scans
- Used sculpting software to refine end product

Incinerator Studios - Digital Artist 2007 - 2009

- Worked on various PS2 and Wii titles based on popular IPs
- Modeled, unwrapped, and textured art assets & environments

EDUCATION

Austin Community College - Java Development Program	Sept 2017 - Present
Grow With Google - Udacity Scholarship - Front End Dev	Jan 2018 - Present
General Assembly Austin - Web Development Immersive	Nov 2016 - Feb 2017
The Art Institute San Diego - Game Art & Design	2005